


pylon_point_1 = { x: 150, y: 902, grad_left: "green-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_2 = { x: 12, y: 976, grad_left: "lime-grad", grad_front: "yellow-grad", grad_right: "cyan-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_3 = { x: 512, y: 976, grad_left: "grey-grad", grad_front: "yellow-grad", grad_right: "blue-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_4 = { x: 912, y: 976, grad_left: "cyan-grad", grad_front: "red-grad", grad_right: "grey-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_5 = { x: 1312, y: 976, grad_left: "blue-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;

pylon_point_6 = { x: -412, y: 776, grad_left: "lime-grad", grad_front: "green-grad", grad_right: "cyan-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_7 = { x: 12, y: 776, grad_left: "yellow-grad", grad_front: "red-grad", grad_right: "grey-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_8 = { x: 512, y: 776, grad_left: "grey-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "cyan-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_9 = { x: 912, y: 776, grad_left: "green-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_10 = { x: 1312, y: 776, grad_left: "green-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;

pylon_point_11 = { x: -412, y: 576, grad_left: "green-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_12 = { x: 12, y: 576, grad_left: "lime-grad", grad_front: "green-grad", grad_right: "cyan-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_13 = { x: 512, y: 576, grad_left: "yellow-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "grey-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_14 = { x: 912, y: 576, grad_left: "red-grad", grad_front: "grey-grad", grad_right: "cyan-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_15 = { x: 1312, y: 576, grad_left: "green-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "blue-grad" }; // = aways_left;

pylon_point_16 = { x: -412, y: 376, grad_left: "lime-grad", grad_front: "yellow-grad", grad_right: "cyan-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_17 = { x: 12, y: 376, grad_left: "cyan-grad", grad_front: "grey-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_18 = { x: 512, y: 376, grad_left: "grey-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "yellow-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_19 = { x: 912, y: 376, grad_left: "green-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_20 = { x: 1312, y: 376, grad_left: "green-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;

pylon_point_21 = { x: -412, y: 176, grad_left: "blue-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_22 = { x: 12, y: 176, grad_left: "lime-grad", grad_front: "yellow-grad", grad_right: "cyan-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_23 = { x: 512, y: 176, grad_left: "grey-grad", grad_front: "red-grad", grad_right: "cyan-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_24 = { x: 912, y: 176, grad_left: "blue-grad", grad_front: "grey-grad", grad_right: "yellow-grad" }; // = aways_left;
pylon_point_25 = { x: 1312, y: 176, grad_left: "green-grad", grad_front: "blue-grad", grad_right: "red-grad" }; // = aways_left;

